PROFILE

Computer Science graduate with one year experience. I am passionate about software development and Machine and Deep Learning. Able to work well on own initiative or as a part of a team. Always keen on taking new challenges and learning new things.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

UNIVERSITAT POMPEU FABRA | 2015 - 2019 **AVERAGE MARK: 8**

- ONE SEMESTER EXCHANGE IN MUNICH AT THE TECHNISCHE UNIVERSITÄT MÜNCHEN
 - TWO MASTER COURSES:
 - CLOUD COMPUTING.
 - INFORMATION AND KNOWLEDGE MANAGEMENT.

LANGUAGES

ENLGISH

FIRST CERTIFICATE IN ENGLISH (FCE) - B2 - GRADE A -WITH ADVANCED CERTIFICATE IN ENGLISH (CAE) - C1 LEVEL

GERMAN

B2 LEVEL CERTIFICATE ESCUELA OFICAL DE IDIOMAS DE DRASSANES BARCELONA

SPANISH

MOTHER TOUNGE, NATIVE SPEAKER INSTITUTO DE TORREDEMBARRA

CATALAN

MOTHER TOUNGE, NATIVE SPEAKER INSTITUTO DE TORREDEMBARRA

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK JUNIOR ENGINEER

FOURTHHUB S.L. | OCT 2019 - JUL. 2020

- Lead Engineer of the software development team.
- Design and develop all the infrastructure of the product.
- Angular, Spring, MySQL, Liquibase, Python and AWS (S3, EC2...)

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

AWERTY SERVICIOS INFORMATICOS | JUL 2017 - SEP 2017 & JUL 2018 - SEP 2018

- Intern in the development department.
- iusUp development: https://www.iusup.es/.
- Languages used: C#, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

SKILLS

- Cloud Computing with AWS and Docker Compose.
- Object oriented programming: C++, Java y Python.
- Machine and Deep Learning with Weka, PyTorch, TorchText.
- Android mobile programming, Git, Windows and Linux (Ubuntu). For more details check my github repository



https://github.com/oscarfont



ÓSCAR FONT

COMPUTER SCIENCE GRADUATE

CONTACT



+34 649 220 442



✓ oscar.font99@gmail.com



in https://es.linkedin.com/in/ofont99/en